(Amy:)Your thoughts and ideas come
from you, not from your anxiety.
(Sheldon:)Hmm, perhaps.
(Sheldon:)But I'm not taking
the cap off.
(Amy:)It's one thing to make
yourself miserable,
(Amy:)but you're making everyone
around you miserable, too.
(Amy:)Now, I'm telling you for the
last time-- take the cap off.
Oh!
(Sheldon:)Really?
(Sheldon:)What if I don't?
(Sheldon:)And before you answer that,
can I have my dessert?
(Sheldon:)And then she
threw me out.
(Sheldon:)Me, her very
own boyfriend.
(Sheldon:)When all I've done is try
to help humanity reach
a more profound understanding
of the world we live in.
(Man:)Yeah, well, women--
(Man:)what are you gonna do?
(Sheldon:)I knew you'd understand,
Armadillo Isaac Newton.
(Leonard:)Okay...
(Leonard:)Here we are.